STAN HILL

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER



Phone: +48571244563 +380677882960

Email: stasgill@gmail.com

Linkedin

GitHub

Telegram

Location:

Poland, Gdańsk

ABOUT

Hello I'am a Full-stack developer with three and more years experience in developing of web and mobile application. Worked in big international team in sphere of sport streaming service and gambling industry. Familiar with business process and goals. Friendly for learning new technologies and use best pattern an approaches in developing applications.

MY STACK

JavaScript, **React**, React Hooks, Redux, MobX, TypeScript, Jest, Sass, Html, Css, Webpack, **Node js**, Express js, Mongo DB, FireBase, React Native, Expo.

WORK EXPERIENCE

EYAS gaming / Front-end developer position — from 2020 to 2022.

While working for the company took part in the development of gambling web application. Implemented a new ability to control players and games also improved and optimised the code base and fixed bugs. Worked in big international team from Europe, England and Indian region.

DAZN / Front-end developer position — from 2022 to 2023.

While working for the company took part in the development of sport streaming web application. Implement functionality related to updating the subscription and changing the current one. Took part of improving and optimisation in error handling.

EDUCATION

GoIT course of Full-stack developer : 2018-2019 Odessa National Academy - Bachelor's degree : 2008 -2013;

LANGUAGES

English - upper intermediate. **Ukrainian** - native speaker. **Russian** - native speaker. **Polish** - under study.

SKILLS

I have a good soft skills, easily find a common language with team members and always friendly and open to dialogue. Work and interaction in a large international team, understanding of business tasks and goals. Constant self-development and self-learning, desire to help businesses and improve people's lives.